Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Moving images and audio recordings
  - Video cassettes
    - Unique
      - Planet rock-Afrika Bambaataa & the Soulsonic Force, 1982; V-9936; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa; 00:44:30; VHS (Box 96)
        Live performance by Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force. Bambaataa material first 44 minutes, the remainder is television. Only Bambaataa material was digitized.
      - Afrika Bambaataa and family at Nation of Islam, Undated; V-9960; 03:48:46; VHS (Box 96)
        Compilation with Bambaataa and Family at the Nation of Islam; No More God Games Pt. 1 & 2; The Teachings of Nuwaubu; Dr. Malachi Z. York. Digitized as file RMM08094_V09960.
      - Afrika Bambaataa in Naeba, Japan, 2000; V-9964; Afrika Bambaataa; 02:05:25; VHS (Box 96)
        Afrika Bambaataa DJing, b-boying, and other performances. Digitized as file RMM08094_V09964.
        Naeba, Japan
      - Afrika Bambaataa and Soulsonic Force live at Brava's Club '85 in Japan, 1985; V-9966; Afrika Bambaataa; 01:47:55; VHS (Box 96)
        Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force performing live in concert. Backdrop on stage indicates that the location is Brava's Club '85, possibly a music festival in Tokyo Japan. Same as V-9951 and V-9952. Digitized as RMM08094_V09966.
      - Lectures dubbed from video; Zulu Nation on Geraldo Rivera; Universal Zulu Nation meeting, 1999; V-9974; Afrika Bambaataa; 04:47:54; VHS (Box 96)
      - Zulu Nation on B.E.T., Rap City, Tues. Feb 27, 1995, 1995-02-27; V-10020; B.E.T.; 02:18:41; VHS (Box 97)
        Afrika Bambaataa and the Rock Steady Crew being interviewed, dicussion of the 20th aniversary of Zulu Nation, hip hop music videos by Bambaataa and others. This may be part 1. Digitized as file RMM08094_V10020.
      - Soulsonic Force in Boston, Undated; V-10032; Afrika Bambaataa; Betamax (Box 97)
        Boston, Massachusettes
      - Afrika Bambaataa and Time Zone, live in Paris, 1987-06-25; V-10040; Afrika Bambaataa; 00:18:00; U-Matic (Box 97)
        This starts about 20 minutes into the same recording found on V-7190. This is a very clean version so it has been digitized as well. Box says 16' 30" which implies this is a sample of the performance. There's also some editing effects.
        Paris, France
      - Afrika Bambaataa and Soulsonic Force, 1985-06-28; V-10046; VHS (Box 97)
      - Universal Zulu Nation meeting, November 12, 2000, 2000-11-11-2000-11-12; V-10060; Afrika Bambaataa; VHS (Box 97)
      - Universal Zulu Nation meeting-Divide and Conquer, Undated; V-10062; Afrika Bambaataa; VHS (Box 97)
      - Universal Zulu Nation-Unity rally, Undated; V-10063; VHS (Box 97)
        The 25th Hip Hop Anniversary, Part 2., Universal Zulu Nation
      - Universal Zulu Nation meeting, November 2, 1994, 1994-11-02; V-10233; Afrika Bambaataa; 00:13:01; VHS-C (Box 97)
        Video from meeting with two women giving talks, one about HIV.
      - Universal Zulu Nation meeting, December 7, 1993, 1993-12-07; V-10235; Afrika Bambaataa; VHS-C (Box 97)
      - Universal Zulu Nation meeting, November 3, 1993, 1993-11-03; V-10236; Afrika Bambaataa; VHS-C (Box 97)
      - Afrika Bambaataa in Rome, 1992; V-10237; Afrika Bambaataa; VHS-C (Box 97)
        Rome, Italy
      - Universal Zulu Nation meeting, February 23, 1994, 1994-02-23; V-10238; Afrika Bambaataa; VHS-C (Box 97)
      - Outbreak Virus Ebola Disease Wipe out of Americans and World, Undated; V-7180; VHS (Box 97)
      - Universal Zulu Nation presents the Mystical Meeting of the Minds (Day 3), May 16, 2004 (vol. 1), 2004-05-16; V-9892; Afrika Bambaataa; 03:41:33; VHS (Box 97)
        Event held at the National Black Theater, organized by the Universal Zulu Nation. Lecture given by Phil Valentine and Q&A. Digitized as file RMM08094_V09892.
      - Bambaataa music videos and hip hop programs on European TV., 1988; V-9917; Afrika Bambaataa; 04:39:02; Betamax (Box 97)
        Compilation of Bambaataa music videos and European shows featuring hip hop including Afrika Bambaataa perfomring "Reckless" on Azzurro 88 (Italian TV show), Bambaataa featured in Nescafe commercials, graffiti artist Brim Fuentes on British TV, documentary about hip hop, and more.
      - James Brown and Afrika Bambaataa recording Unity; Bambaataa on MTV, 1984; V-9918; Afrika Bambaataa; 04:36:19; Betamax (Box 97)
        Behind the scenes of the recording of Unity with Bambaataa and James Brown. Includes Brown being interviewed by Entertainment Tonight. Second half of tape is Bambaataa interviewed and other videos on MTV.
      - Afrika Bambaataa music video b-roll (song unknown), 1987-04-13; V-9920; Melody Movies; 00:12:00; U-Matic (Box 97)
        B-roll for a Bambaataa music video, possibly Nescafe commercial. Features Bambaataa and two others dancing. Creator name taken from tape box.
      - Shout it out-Afrika Bambaataa, 1988; V-9928; 0:04:09; U-Matic (Box 97)
        as labeled, squealing
      - Shout it out-Afrika Bambaataa, 1988; V-9929; 0:04:09; U-Matic (Box 97)
      - History of Rap documentary on BBC Television, 1991; V-9931; Ali, Sharon; Rapido TV & Canal + 1991; 00:56:05; U-Matic (Box 97)
        Creator name taken from closing credits.
      - Beat This!: a Hip Hop history, 1984; V-9939; Fraad, Julie; Ahearn, Charlie; 01:11:00; Betamax (Box 97)
        Documentary about hip hop. Maginificent Force is possibly the production company. Produced by Julie Fraad and directed by Charlie Ahearn.
      - Diana Ross live, Undated; V-9945; 01:35:00; Betamax (Box 97)
        Tape labeled "Zulu Nation live" but did not contain UZN material. Not digitized.
      - Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force live in Tokyo, Japan (part 1), 1985-06-28; V-9951; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa; 01:00:28; U-Matic (Box 97)
        Digitized as file RMM08094_V09951.
      - Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force live in Tokyo, Japan (part 2), 1985-06-28; V-9952; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa; 00:49:38; U-Matic (Box 97)
        Digitized as file RMM08094_V09952.
      - Universal Zulu Nation Detroit chapter, 1995; V-9968; Afrika Bambaataa; 04:48:01; VHS (Box 97)
        Compilation of performances by several different artists, interviews including Outkast, b-boying. Label indicates Universal Zulu Nation Detroit chapter, but seems to be other footage included.
        Detroit, Michigan
      - Check label, 1994; V-9969; Afrika Bambaataa; 01:54:34; VHS (Box 97)
        DJ battle, b-boying, and several different artists and groups performing at Universal Zulu Nation anniversary event including Prince Whipper Whip and Biz Markie.
        Not sure why I've titled this "20th Anniversary" since the content doesn't look like the other 20th anniversary tapes. Jolene: check the labels. Might need to rename.
      - Universal Zulu Nation meetings on UFOs; AIDS; Meeting of the mind; On religion, 1999; V-9983; Afrika Bambaataa; 05:40:18; VHS (Box 97)
      - Shout it out-Afrika Bambaataa, 1988-04-08; V-9995; 0:04:09; U-Matic (Box 97)
      - Rodney Williams interviewing Afrika Bambaataa and the Jungle Brothers, Undated; V-10030; VHS (Box 98)
      - Afrika Bambaataa in Madrid, Span, Undated; V-10031; Afrika Bambaataa; VHS (Box 98)
      - Afrika Bambaataa in Madrid, Span, Undated; V-10031; Afrika Bambaataa; VHS (Box 98)
      - Zulu Festival, 1991, 1991; V-10033; U-Matic (Box 98)
        Zulu Festival raw footage; On camera-off camera Rt. 30 w/ Michael Berman, 10/17/91; "The Drifters & Terry King"
      - Rap concert in memory of Yusef Hawkins, 1989-09-17; V-10038; VHS (Box 98)
      - Afrika Bambaataa in Zagreb, Croatia, 1996-02-18-1996-02-19; V-10053; Afrika Bambaataa; PAL (Box 98)
      - Zulu Nation at the Love Parade, 2000-07-08; V-10080; Hi8 (Box 98)
        Zulu Nation at the Love Parade, July 8, 2000. Sat. Tape 1.
      - Afrika Bambaataa in Orlando, Paris, London, Undated; V-10081; Afrika Bambaataa; "Notes"; Hi8 (Box 98)
      - Michael's tour with Bambaataa, Undated; V-10082; Hi8 (Box 98)
      - Zulu Nation in Milan, Italy and Austria, 2000-06-19; V-10083; Afrika Bambaataa; Hi8 (Box 98)
      - Afrika Bambaataa in Birmingham, United Kingdom, 2001-03-10; V-10086; Afrika Bambaataa; Hi8 (Box 98)
      - Afrika Bambaataa in Middlesbrough, United Kingdom, 2001-03-03; V-10217; Afrika Bambaataa; Hi8 (Box 98)
      - Afrika Bambaataa in Cardiff, Wales, 2001-03-16; V-10218; Afrika Bambaataa; Hi8 (Box 98)
      - Zulu Nation in Switzerland, 2000-07; V-10219; Afrika Bambaataa; Hi8 (Box 98)
      - Afrika Bambaataa in Amsterdam, Cork, and Glasgow, 2001; V-10220; Afrika Bambaataa; Hi8 (Box 98)
      - Afrika Bambaataa in Koln, Germany, 2000-06-30; V-10222; Afrika Bambaataa; Hi8 (Box 98)
      - Afrika Bambaataa in Zagreb, Croatia, 2000-06-25; V-10223; Afrika Bambaataa; Hi8 (Box 98)
      - Zulu Nation at the Love Parade, 2000-07-08; V-10224; Afrika Bambaataa; Hi8 (Box 98)
        Zulu nation at Love Parade, Sat. July 8, 2000
      - Zulu Nation in Heidelberg, Germany and Leftfield at Montreaux Jazz Festival, 2000-07-21; V-10225; Hi8 (Box 98)
      - Rally, Undated; V-10226; Hi8 (Box 98)
      - Afrika Bambaataa in Leeds, United Kingdom, 2001-03-12; V-10227; Afrika Bambaataa; Hi8 (Box 98)
      - Universal Zulu Nation meeting, April 2, 2003, 2003-04-02; V-10228; Afrika Bambaataa; Hi8 (Box 98)
      - Afrika Bambaataa in United Kingdom, 2001; V-10229; Afrika Bambaataa; Hi8 (Box 98)
        Afrika Bambaataa, Zulus in UK
      - Afrika Bambaataa in Glasgow, Scotland, 2001; V-10230; Afrika Bambaataa; Hi8 (Box 98)
      - Afrika Bambaataa at the 6th Element rave, Randall Island, NYC, 2000-07-10; V-10231; Hi8 (Box 98)
      - Afrika Bambaata in Sardinia, Italy, 2000; V-10234; Afrika Bambaataa; VHS-C (Box 98)
        Saridinia, Italy
      - Twentieth Universal Zulu Nation Anniversary, 1994; V-9907; Afrika Bambaataa; PAL (Box 98)
        Not a dupe of 7202. Seems unique: Press conference; 40 mins female dj contest; 1 hour walking around with a guy, interviews
      - Afrika Bambaataa: Sho Nuff Funky, Undated; V-9913; VHS (Box 98)
      - [Unknown], Undated; V-9970; Betamax (Box 98)
        zulu
      - Looking for the Perfect Beat-Afrika Bambaataa and Soulsonic Force, rough cut, Undated; V-10006; Tommy Boy Records; U-Matic (Box 99)
        Looking For The Perfect Beat, Soul Sonic Force, Rough cut -7'00", Tommy Boy Records, Video mix J. Jason / D.Cornyetz
      - Express-Busy Bee, Undated; V-10007; Uni Records; VHS (Box 99)
        Uni Records, David Fasano, Busy Bee "Express", 4:35
      - World Destruction-Time Zone, 1985-03-14; V-10011; Celluloid Records; U-Matic (Box 99)
        Celluloid records, Time Zone: "World Destruction" (3/14/85)
      - Beat This!: a Hip Hop history, 1984; V-10024; VHS (Box 99)
        Tape starts with "Beat This" documentary (1984) although it's labeled "Bombin'". Description of "Bombin"--Hip Hop History Bombin' (made for European TV): Afrika Bambaataa, Kook Herc, Cold Crush Brothers, Lisa Lee, Sha-Rock, Soulsonic Force, Jazzy Jay, Brim, Bio. Made for European TV.
      - The Freshest Kids, 2002; V-10027; Brotherhood Films; VHS (Box 99)
        Brotherhood films-The Freshest Kids, 323.933.4402, Afrika Bambaataa & KLB. Documentary about hip hop and b-boy pioneers
      - Leftfield "Afrika Shox", 1999-05-21; V-9914 (Box 99)
        Music video for Leftfield's "Afrika Shox" feat. Bambaataa
      - Looking for the Perfect Beat-Afrika Bambaataa and Soulsonic Force, Undated; V-9921; VHS (Box 99)
        Looking For The Perfect Beat, Soul Sonic Force, Old mix
      - Looking for the Perfect Beat-Afrika Bambaataa and Soulsonic Force, Undated; V-9922; U-Matic (Box 99)
        Sould Sonic Force, Looking for the Perfect Beat
      - Ndodemnyama (Free South Africa)- Hip Hop Artists Against Apartheid, 1989; V-9923; Ndodemnyama- "Free South Africa", Off-line cut; VHS (Box 99)
      - Ndodemnyama (Free South Africa)- Hip Hop Artists Against Apartheid, 1989-10-17; V-9926; U-Matic (Box 99)
        Ndodemnyona- "Free South Africa" (Two versions)
      - Reckless-Afrika Bamaataa & UB40, 1988; V-9932; VHS (Box 99)
        UB40 / Afrika Bambaataa and Family "Reckless"
      - Planet rock-Afrika Bambaataa & the Soulsonic Force, Undated; V-9937; Tommy Boy Records; U-Matic (Box 99)
        Planet Rock, Soul Sonic Force, 7:30; NTSC, Color, Stero ©1982 Tommy Boy Records
      - Soca Fever-Afrika Bambaataa, 1991; V-9938; U-Matic (Box 99)
        (u-matic)
      - Street happiness-Enzo Avitable & Afrika Bambaataa, 1988; V-9950; U-Matic (Box 99)
      - Universal Zulu Nation at the House of Blues, B-boy summit (part 1), 1998; V-9959; Afrika Bambaataa; VHS (Box 99)
        Same beginning as V-9958-B-boying and Bambaataa djing at House of Blues; B-boying competition or exhibition
      - Get up and dance-Afrika Bambaataa vs. Carpe Diem, 1990; V-9987; Multiply Records (Box 99)
        Afrika Bambaataa vs. Carpe Diem - "Get up and dance". Duration: 3'40" - Multiply records
      - Planet rock-Afrika Bambaataa & the Soulsonic Force, Undated; V-9991; Tommy Boy Records; 0:04:00; U-Matic (Box 99)
        Tommy Boy Music, Inc. Afrika Bambaataa & the Soulsonic Force "Planet Rock" (4:00)
      - Ndodemnyama (Free South Africa)- Hip Hop Artists Against Apartheid, 1989-12-13; V-9994; VHS (Box 99)
        South Africa Artists, "Free South Africa" Version 1&2
      - Unity-Afrika Bambaataa & James Brown, 1984-10-01; V-9999; U-Matic (Box 99)
      - Tommy Boy Records video compilation reel, 1989-08-24; V-10005; Tommy Boy Records; 0:33:00; VHS (Box 100)
        Tommy Boy Records video compilation reel, radio & retail version (33:00). Queen Latifah promotional video, Too Poetic, De La Soul "Say No Go", Cold Cut "People hold on"
      - Afrika Bambaataa videos; The 30th Grammy Awards, 1988; V-10012; Betamax (Box 100)
      - Videos-James Brown, Afrika Bambaataa, & UB40; Soul Train Awards, 1988; V-10013; Betamax (Box 100)
      - Afrika Bambaataa on DOC TV, 1988-04; V-10014; PAL (Box 100)
        Afrika Bambaataa, DOC TV - 18119 April 1988
      - Afrika Bambaataa and Time Zone at Paris Place (Part one of two), 1987-06-25; V-10029; Afrika Bambaataa; VHS (Box 100)
      - Universal Zulu Nation in Orlando?, Undated; V-10232; Afrika Bambaataa; VHS-C (Box 100)
        Orlando, Florida
      - Sixteenth Universal Zulu Nation anniversary, 1990; V-9897; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 100)
        Dallas-performance outdoors Special Ed.; 16th Zulu Anniversary indoors MC w/tuxedo (same as V-9898 likely)
      - Twentieth Universal Zulu Nation anniversary, 1994; V-9905; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 100)
        MC battles, DJ battles, b-boying
      - De La Soul on Club MTV, 1989-05-19; V-9930; U-Matic (Box 100)
        MTV Networks Inc. Club MTV, Show #228, 30:00, 5/19/89; Guest: De La Soul
      - Reckless-Afrika Bamaataa & UB40, 1988; V-9933; EMI Records Ltd.; 0:04:09; U-Matic (Box 100)
        Afrika Bambaataa & UB40 "Reckless" 4:09 ©1988 EMI Records Ltd.
      - Reckless-Afrika Bamaataa & UB40, 1988; V-9934; EMI Records Ltd.; 0:04:09; U-Matic (Box 100)
      - X-tra butter-Tommy Boy Music, Inc. Featuring: Afrika Bambaataa & the Soulsonic Force, Queen Latifah, House of Pain, Naughty by Nature, 1990; V-9935; Tommy Boy Music; VHS (Box 100)
        Tommy Boy Music, Inc. "X-TRA BUTTER" Featuring: Queen Latifah-"How do I love thee"; House of Pain-"Jump Around"; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soulsonic Force- "Planet Rock" (Re-edit); Naughty By Nature-"Uptown Anthem"/
      - Afrika Bambaataa and Time Zone at Paris Palace (Part one of two), 1987-06-25; V-9946; Afrika Bambaataa; U-Matic (Box 100)
        From label: Bambaataa/Time Zone Paris Palace 25/6/87 Part I (Just one camera among 3 and not the tape sound), Dur: 62 mins.
      - Afrika Bambaataa and Time Zone at Paris Palace (Part two of two), 1987-06-25; V-9947; Afrika Bambaataa; U-Matic (Box 100)
        From label: Bambaataa/Time Zone Paris Palace 25/6/87 Part II (Just one camera among 3 and not the tape sound), Dur: 20:23 mins.
      - Bambaataa and Family live at the Palace in Paris, France June 25, 1987 Part I, 1987-06-25; V-9948; Afrika Bambaataa; U-Matic (Box 100)
      - Bambaataa and Family live at the Palace in Paris, France June 25, 1987 Part II, 1987-06-25; V-9949; Afrika Bambaataa; U-Matic (Box 100)
      - Afrika Bambaataa and Time Zone at Paris Palace (Part two of two), 1987-06-25; V-9953; Afrika Bambaataa; VHS (Box 100)
        May be recorded at slower speed, music is sped up
      - Universal Zulu Nation in Orlando, Undated; V-9961; Afrika Bambaataa; VHS (Box 100)
        Same Bambaataa H.O.B. dj performance as V-9958 and V-9959; Maseo and Bambaataa in France (also same as V-9958)
      - Universal Zulu Nation anniversary, 1990; V-9972; Afrika Bambaataa; VHS (Box 100)
        Zulu Nation anniversary, Bambaataa setting up to DJ and saying hi to others. Introduction. MCs performing (may be duplicate of V-9898 and 9899
      - Geraldo Rivera: Zulu Nation women vs. KKK women, Undated; V-9975; Afrika Bambaataa; VHS (Box 100)
        Ricki Lake show ffwed, Geraldo show Zulu Queens vs. KKK women
      - Geraldo Rivera: Zulu Nation women vs. KKK women, Undated; V-9977; VHS (Box 100)
        Geraldo show again.
      - Just get up and dance-Afrika Bambaataa, Undated; V-9988 (Box 100)
      - Ndodemnyama (Free South Africa)- Hip Hop Artists Against Apartheid, 1989-10-17; V-9993; U-Matic (Box 100)
      - Zulu Nation Information Takeover: Iron Mountain / United Nations, Waco the Big Lie, Millenium 2000, Undated; V-10001; VHS (Box 101)
        As labeled--videos for Zulu Nation meeting
      - Zulu Nation Information: 1. Day 51, 2. Clinton Chronicles; 3. Dr. Lorraine Day on AIDS update, 4. Lucifer 2000, 5. UFOs, Undated; V-10004; VHS (Box 101)
        Day 51; Clinton Chronicles; Dr. Lorraine Day on AIDS; Lucifer 2000; UFOs
      - Zulu Nation on Rap City, 1996, 1996-04-23; V-10017; VHS (Box 101)
        Afrika Bambaataa "Funk this party out", credits say "1st hour, rec. 4/23/96, air 4/24/96" Bambaataa being interviewed by Big Lez
      - Zulu Nation on Rap City, 1995, Part 1?, 1995-02-27; V-10021; VHS (Box 101)
        Zulu Nation on Rap City, B.E.T., Monday Feb. 27, 1995, Part 1
      - Zulu Nation women vs. KKK women on the Geraldo Rivera Show (long version), 1995; V-10025; VHS (Box 101)
      - Afrika Bambaataa and Family on Italian TV shows, 1988; V-10028; VHS (Box 101)
        Bologna sett. 88 "Vota voce"; Milano dic. 88 "Disco ring"; Roma genn. 89 "Stasera Lino"; Milano dic. 88 "1,2,3 Iovanotti";Napoli ott. 88 "live E.Avitabile".
      - The South Bank Show, Zulu Nation of Japan, Undated; V-10064; VHS (Box 101)
      - Zulu masters #1, Undated; V-10065; VHS (Box 101)
        Zulu Masters-1: 1. UFO's secrets of the the Third Reich, 2. Illuminati survival colonies
      - The Zulu files #2: 1. IRS-Federal Reserve, 2. George Green, 3. William Copper, 4. Bo-Gritz healing, 5. Masonic Lodge, 6. Craig Heweth, John F. Kennedy, Undated; V-10066; VHS (Box 101)
        "American, the Fed and the IRS: a legacy of greed" and other assorted documentaries.
      - Zulu masters #2, Undated; V-10067; VHS (Box 101)
        Zulu tape #2, UFOs. Unedited beginning/set-up of interview,
      - Zulu masters #3, Undated; V-10068; VHS (Box 101)
        Interview about UFOs
      - Zulu masters #4, Undated; V-10069; VHS (Box 101)
        Rocket planes, aircrafts, UFOs
      - Zulu masters #6, Undated; V-10070; VHS (Box 101)
        Beamships
      - Zulu Nation Unity meeting: 1. Young Lords, 2. Aruthur X, 3. The Prophet, 1993, 1993; V-10075; VHS (Box 101)
      - Zulu Nation in Helsinki, Finland, 2000-07-06; V-10084; Afrika Bambaataa; Hi8 (Box 101)
        Zulu Nation in Helsinki Finland, July 6, 2000
      - Hip Hop conferenece meeting in Chicago with Zulu Nation, Feb. 2001, 2001-02; V-10085; Hi8 (Box 101)
      - Afrika Bambaataa in Newcastle, United Kingdom, 2001-03-13; V-10087; Afrika Bambaataa; Hi8 (Box 101)
        Afrika Bambaataa at Newcastle University, Newcastle, England, Tuesday March 13, 2001
      - Afrika Bambaataa in Stoke, England, 2001-03-14; V-10221; Afrika Bambaataa; Hi8 (Box 101)
        Afrika Bambaataa, Reckless Club, Stoke, England. Wed. Mar. 14, 2001
      - Universal Zulu Nation meeting, December 8, 2001, 2001-12-08; V-9888 (Box 101)
        Zulu nation presents: Phil Valentine - 2001, Meeting of the Minds II
      - Twenty-fifth Universal Zulu Nation Anniversary, 1999; V-9896 (Box 101)
        25th Hip Hop Anniversary, Universal Zulu Nation, M #1. Performance by 2 MC's, Performance by Cold Crush Bros, Rotating DJ's including Jazzy Jay with Bambaataa MCing, other MC performing (duplicate of V-9895)
      - Sixteenth Universal Zulu Nation Anniversary (tape 1), 1990; V-9899 (Box 101)
        Same content as seen in V-9898 and V-9899, but not the Dallas performances
      - Seventeenth Universal Zulu Nation, 1991; V-9902 (Box 101)
        Music and dancing, Lovebug Starski.
      - Universal Zulu Nation meeting, January 29, 1997, 1997-01-29; V-9909 (Box 101)
        U.Z.N. Meeting on UFO's & Aliens. Wed. Jan. 29, 1997 at the Point (broken? tape)
      - Just get up and dance-Afrika Bambaataa, Undated; V-9910; Afrika Bambaataa, Just Get Up and Dance (Box 101)
        Credits in italian.
      - Just get up and dance-Afrika Bambaataa;EMF;Jaz, Undated; V-9911 (Box 101)
        EMF "Lies" (4:39); The Jaz "A Groove" (This is what u rap 2) (4:16); Afrika Bambaataa "Just get up and dance" (4:42)
      - Get up and dance-Afrika Bambaataa vs. Carpe Diem, 1990; V-9916; Multiply Records (Box 101)
      - Ndodemnyama (Free South Africa)- Hip Hop Artists Against Apartheid, 1989-10-17; V-9924; U-Matic (Box 101)
        Umatic
      - Ndodemnyama (Free South Africa)- Hip Hop Artists Against Apartheid, 1989-10-17; V-9925; U-Matic (Box 101)
        Actually is Ndodemnyama-"Free South Africa"
      - Like It Is - Afrika Bambaataa, Harry Allen, Talib Kweli, 2000; V-9940; VHS (Box 101)
        "Like It Is" episode on Hip Hop featuring panel with Harry Allen, Afrika Bambaataa, Talib Kweli
      - Unity-Afrika Bambaataa & James Brown, Undated; V-9942; Unity, not so clear copy of Rapmania & Electric Dance Hop, Afrika Bambaataa & Family; VHS (Box 101)
        Afrika Bambaataa and Family performing "Unity" on Rapmania, then a recording of a conference on Muslims and Christians. Opens with speaker from the African American Catholic Congregation talking about coming together with Nation of Islam.
      - Rapp's Underground, 1990; V-9943; VHS (Box 101)
        Rapp's Undergroup Video Show, interview with MC Hammer and debut of his video "Help the Children"
      - Street happiness-Enzo Avitable & Afrika Bambaataa, 1988; V-9956; VHS (Box 101)
      - Leftfield with Afrika Bambaataa at the Lynxx Legends, Undated; V-9963; VHS (Box 101)
        Chaka Khan, Grace Jones, Leftfield, Afrika Bambaataa in Ibiza. Duplicate of V-9912
      - Trouble Funk live in Japan, Doin' their hits, Undated; V-9965; VHS (Box 101)
      - Zulu queens vs. Ku Klux Klan women; Prime Time; Bo dropping wisdom, Undated; V-9976; VHS (Box 101)
        Geraldo show again; Speaker at a meeting, likely a ZN meeting; Primetime
      - Universal Zulu Nation meeting, Who are the real Latinos?, 1990-1999; V-9978; VHS (Box 101)
        As labeled.
      - Universal Zulu Nation meeting, Who are the real Latinos?, 1990-1999; V-9979; VHS (Box 101)
      - Universal Zulu Nation meeting, Who are the real Latinos?, 1990-1999; V-9981; VHS (Box 101)
        Universal Zulu Nation meeting. Who are the real Latinos? Minister Abdullah Muhammed.
      - Universal Zulu Nation meeting; Cosmic slop; UFOs, 1990-1999; V-9982; VHS (Box 101)
        Cosmic slop; UFO's (Black people); UZN meeting with speaker Richard Perez; activists from the Young Lords party; introduction by Bam.
      - Just get up and dance-Afrika Bambaataa;EMF;Jaz, Undated; V-9989 (Box 101)